William Safire Papers
William Safire Papers
- Writings
  - Books
    - Lend Me Your Ears, 2nd edition
      - Miscellaneous - Collected items (Box 385)
    - Lend Me Your Ears, 3rd edition
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 385)
      - Index (Box 386)
      - Publicity (Box 386)
      - Recommendations (Box 386)
    - Lend Me Your Ears, 4th edition
      - Correspondence (Box 386)
    - Let A Simile Be Your Umbrella
      - Correspondence (Box 386)
      - Acknowledgements (Box 386)
      - Contract (Box 386)
      - Columns copies, 5 folders (Box 386)
      - Fan letters (Box 386)
      - Permission forms, Terry Allen art (Box 386)
      - Reader permissions, 3 folders (Box 386)
      - Reader permissions, 4 folders (Box 387)
      - Reader permissions charts, 2 folders (Box 387)
      - Research notes
        - Adultery (Box 387)
        - Adverbs (Box 387)
        - Aha! (Box 387)
        - Also vs. as well (Box 387)
        - Arabic words in English (Box 387)
        - Arcane (Box 387)
        - As We Know It (Box 387)
        - Asian loanwords (Box 387)
        - Bank Morris (Box 387)
        - Bank, "I'm not sure" (Box 387)
        - Been there, done that/Same old, same old (Box 387)
        - Between us/ourselves (Box 387)
        - The blahs (Box 387)
        - Bloopie Awards 1995, 3 folders (Box 388)
        - Blue Dog demo (Box 388)
        - Book plugs, 2 folders (Box 388)
        - Books/soft landing (Box 388)
        - Britishisms (Box 388)
        - Brung/drug (Box 388)
        - Buchanan, James (Box 388)
        - Bugger (Box 388)
        - Bumf/bumph (Box 388)
        - Burdensharing (Box 388)
        - Cack-handed (Box 388)
        - Call (Box 388)
        - Canard/duck (Box 388)
        - Carrot and stick (Box 388)
        - Catalogue errors, 2 folders (Box 388)
        - Central/Eastern Europe (Box 388)
        - Children's language (Box 388)
        - Chunky chose (Box 388)
        - Cliffhanger (Box 388)
        - Clinton: raise and flaunt (Box 388)
        - Clone (Box 388)
        - Close (Box 389)
        - Closure/cloture (Box 389)
        - Coffee (Box 389)
        - Congressional Record and Newt Gingrich (Box 389)
        - Conspiracy theory (Box 389)
        - Crumpled v. wrinkled (Box 389)
        - Day One (Box 389)
        - Deadheat (Box 389)
        - Dean, doyenne, doyen (Box 389)
        - Dee-cline De-fense (Box 389)
        - Downhill/uphill (Box 389)
        - Downsize/duh (Box 389)
        - Dysfunction (Box 389)
        - Elite Establishment Egghead (Box 389)
        - (dash) ess suffix (Box 389)
        - Exit strategy (Box 389)
        - Experiment with (Box 389)
        - Extremist (Box 389)
        - Facially valid (Box 389)
        - Fair shake (Box 389)
        - Falsely shouting fire (Box 389)
        - Famously (Box 389)
        - Fizzy water (Box 389)
        - Flaunt, flout (Box 389)
        - Fleas is Good for a Dog (Box 389)
        - Forgo vs. forego (Box 389)
        - Four-letter words (Box 389)
        - Fuhgeddaboutit (Box 389)
        - Full-bore, small-bore, large-bore (Box 389)
        - Full-frontal (Box 389)
        - Future English/foreign terms (Box 390)
        - Galoot (Box 390)
        - Gauntlet (Box 390)
        - Gaza strip/West Bank (Box 390)
        - Gazillion (Box 390)
        - Gifts of gab (Box 390)
        - Go south (Box 390)
        - Golden oldie (Box 390)
        - Goldilocks Recovery (Box 390)
        - Goo-goo (Box 390)
        - Gotcha! (Box 390)
        - Gotcha! Gang Strikes Again (Box 390)
        - Gotham (Box 390)
        - Grouse (Box 390)
        - Grow the company (Box 390)
        - Handover (Box 390)
        - Hard way (Box 390)
        - Hardscrabble (Box 390)
        - Helluva (Box 390)
        - Helmich (Box 390)
        - High tea (Box 390)
        - Hillary Clinton's speech in Beijing (Box 390)
        - Hillary-ese (Box 390)
        - Hissy fit (Box 390)
        - Hush money (Box 390)
        - "I Led the Pigeons to the Flag" (Box 390)
        - Icon (Box 390)
        - I'm not sure that… (Box 390)
        - Incontinent (Box 390)
        - Interconnectedness (Box 390)
        - Internet terms (Box 390)
        - Ish (Box 390)
        - Jade/jaded (Box 391)
        - Janus words (Box 391)
        - Jersey (Box 391)
        - Jury-rigged (Box 391)
        - Just (Box 391)
        - Just driving by (Box 391)
        - Knee pants, knickers plus fours, knickerbockers (Box 391)
        - Kwanzaa (Box 391)
        - Long in the tooth (Box 391)
        - Maskirovka/surveille/palindromedaries (Box 391)
        - May v. might (Box 391)
        - Mean spirited/going negative (Box 391)
        - Mistakes 1994, 1995 (Box 391)
        - Mixed metaphors (Box 391)
        - Momentarily (Box 391)
        - Mother's milk (Box 391)
        - Mull/gauntlet (Box 391)
        - Neck down (Box 391)
        - Necking and synonyms (Box 391)
        - Noogie (Box 391)
        - Nuts/psycholbabble (Box 391)
        - Of Hacks and TK (Box 391)
        - OJ Simpson trial (Box 391)
        - Old Testament/first testament (Box 391)
        - Older people terms (Box 392)
        - One picture is worth… (Box 392)
        - Or what? (Box 392)
        - Out of the box (Box 392)
        - Pair of pants (Box 392)
        - Paragraphing (Box 392)
        - Paramount (Box 392)
        - Password (Box 392)
        - Pastie/patsy (Box 392)
        - Philadelphia lawyer (Box 392)
        - Pinker, Steven, 2 folders (Box 392)
        - Pinprick (Box 392)
        - Pixel (Box 392)
        - Pollyanna (Box 392)
        - Poly (Box 392)
        - Powder dry (Box 392)
        - Proctor and Gamble case (Box 392)
        - Prone and supine (Box 392)
        - Proofs 3/30/97-6/29/97 (Box 392)
        - Proximity talks (Box 392)
        - Punmeister (Box 392)
        - Puns (Box 392)
        - Puns, 4 folders (Box 393)
        - Push technology (Box 393)
        - Push-polling (Box 393)
        - Put up or shut up (Box 393)
        - Quack (doctor) (Box 393)
        - Quantum (Box 393)
        - Queing up (Box 393)
        - Quondam (Box 393)
        - Real time (Box 393)
        - Recision/rescission (Box 393)
        - Reduced increase (Box 393)
        - Remediated (Box 393)
        - Retronyms (Box 393)
        - Ringer and stack the deck (Box 393)
        - Road kill (Box 393)
        - Road rage (Box 393)
        - Robust (Box 393)
        - Roll someone's pant leg up on him (Box 393)
        - Schmuck (Box 393)
        - Scupper (Box 393)
        - Seminal (Box 393)
        - Series of (Box 393)
        - Singular v. plural (Box 393)
        - Snuck (Box 393)
        - Soccer mom (Box 394)
        - Spinner Spun (Box 394)
        - Spookspeak (Box 394)
        - Squash/squish like a bug (Box 394)
        - Squeaker (Box 394)
        - Stake holder (Box 394)
        - Step aside, step down, stand down (Box 394)
        - Stuffing stockers (Box 394)
        - Stylish books and knobs (Box 394)
        - Submarine (verb) (Box 394)
        - Sunk/shrunk- past verbs (Box 394)
        - Take the DARE (Box 394)
        - Tchotchkes (Box 394)
        - Than I/me (Box 394)
        - That Certain Age (Box 394)
        - That's where the money is (Box 394)
        - There's/here's (Box 394)
        - "They shoot horses, don't they?" (Box 394)
        - Time cover: how/could (Box 394)
        - Time Line (Box 394)
        - To be sure (Box 394)
        - To vs. with (Box 394)
        - Toast (Box 394)
        - Tony Blair: Naff/chuff (Box 394)
        - Torious interfence (Box 394)
        - Touchy-feely (Box 394)
        - Tweak (Box 394)
        - Unabomber/unabormer (Box 394)
        - Unreconstructed wankers (Box 395)
        - Upside the head (Box 395)
        - Wait on/for (Box 395)
        - Warm fuzzies (Box 395)
        - Whadd'ya Know? Say? (Box 395)
        - When a Justice Needs a Friend, 2 folders (Box 395)
        - When push comes to shove (Box 395)
        - Who/whom (Box 395)
        - Who's John Doe? (Box 395)
        - Without fear or favor (Box 395)
        - Wonk (Box 395)
        - Wronger (Box 395)
      - Thank-you letters (Box 395)
    - The New Language of Politics: A Dictionary of Catchwords, Slogans, and Political Usage
      - Draft, 13 folders; introduction, pages 1-629 (Box 509)
      - Draft, 12 folders; pages 630-1269 (Box 510)
      - Draft, 10 folders; pages 1270-1736, bibliography (Box 511)
    - No Uncertain Terms
      - Freebie list (Box 395)
      - Reader permissions chart (Box 395)
      - Reader permissions letters
        - A (Box 395)
        - B (Box 395)
        - C (Box 395)
        - D (Box 395)
        - E (Box 395)
        - F (Box 395)
        - G (Box 396)
        - H (Box 396)
        - I (Box 396)
        - J (Box 396)
        - K (Box 396)
        - L (Box 396)
        - M (Box 396)
        - N (Box 396)
        - O (Box 396)
        - P (Box 396)
        - R (Box 396)
        - S, 2 folders (Box 396)
        - T (Box 396)
        - U (Box 396)
        - V (Box 396)
        - W, Y, Z (Box 396)
        - Lyrics (Box 397)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 397)
      - Reviews (Box 397)
      - Royalties (Box 397)
      - Research notes
        - Actually (Box 397)
        - Aim at Foot, Fire! (Box 397)
        - And the Horse You Rode In On (Box 397)
        - African-American Names (Box 397)
        - Angst (Box 397)
        - Aptronyms (Box 397)
        - Attractive (Box 397)
        - Au Pair and Nanny (Box 397)
        - Baby Names (Box 397)
        - Backs of the Poor (Box 397)
        - Back to My Roots (Box 397)
        - Bagman (Box 397)
        - BC/AD or BCE/CE, 2 folders (Box 397)
        - Beg the question (Box 397)
        - Belly-button (Box 397)
        - The Best of the Millennium (Box 397)
        - Bible (Box 397)
        - Bill of Rights- origin, 2 folders (Box 398)
        - Bill of Rights- overuse (Box 398)
        - Black Monday (Box 398)
        - Bloopie Awards, 2 folders (Box 398)
        - Blue (Box 398)
        - Blurbs (Box 398)
        - Body slimmers (Box 398)
        - Bone stupid (Box 398)
        - Bread and butter (Box 398)
        - Brooch (Box 398)
        - Bum fuzzle (Box 398)
        - The Bush boys and Drawing Lines in the Sand, 2 folders (Box 398)
        - Canned (Box 398)
        - Canoodle (Box 398)
        - Casino/gaming industry (Box 398)
        - Impeachment-ese (Box 399)
        - Censure (Box 399)
        - Cheesecake (Box 399)
        - Chilling effect (Box 399)
        - China and Taiwan (Box 399)
        - Chopped liver (Box 399)
        - Clara Bow (Box 399)
        - Clinton Fatigue (Box 399)
        - Clown (Box 399)
        - Coinage Ockham's Razor (Box 399)
        - Comfortable in his own skin (Box 399)
        - Common sense/horse sense (Box 399)
        - Compartmentalize (Box 399)
        - Compulsive (Box 399)
        - Compounds-solids with caps (Box 399)
        - Misteak sandwich (Box 399)
        - Content/content provider (Box 399)
        - Content/content provider (Box 400)
        - Contumacious (Box 400)
        - Convoy (Box 400)
        - Crash or plunge (Box 400)
        - Crater (Box 400)
        - Creep (Box 400)
        - Crony capitalism, 2 folders (Box 400)
        - Cuckold (Box 400)
        - Cuckquean (Box 400)
        - Dangle, 2 folders (Box 400)
        - Dead Cat Bounce (Box 400)
        - Deconstruct (Box 400)
        - Defamation (Box 400)
        - Deficits as far as the eye can see (Box 400)
        - Defining moment (Box 401)
        - Disgruntled (Box 401)
        - Dork (Box 401)
        - Drop a dime (Box 401)
        - Dish (Box 401)
        - Dung, Guano, etc. etc. (Box 401)
        - E-Lancers/Easa combining form, 2 folders (Box 401)
        - Edgy- new meaning (Box 401)
        - Emerging Markets (Box 401)
        - Enabler (Box 401)
        - Enough Already (Box 401)
        - The Euro (Box 401)
        - The Euro (Box 402)
        - Eye-roller (Box 402)
        - Extremism (Box 402)
        - Faith-based (Box 402)
        - Fast track, 2 folders (Box 402)
        - Felon (Box 402)
        - Fightback (Box 402)
        - First Things First (Box 402)
        - Fly off the Handle (Box 402)
        - Follower v. Supporter (Box 402)
        - Follow the Proffering Duck (Box 402)
        - Friends with (Box 402)
        - Full monty (Box 402)
        - Fulsome (Box 402)
        - Gaming v. gambling, 2 folders (Box 402)
        - Geek (Box 402)
        - Gentlelady (Box 403)
        - Gentleman's C (Box 403)
        - GI Bill (Box 403)
        - Globality (Box 403)
        - Go figure (Box 403)
        - Grampa (Box 403)
        - Guanxi (Box 403)
        - Guilt by Association (Box 403)
        - Gypsy-Run Through (Box 403)
        - Hair-curling (Box 403)
        - Hair-raising fundraising (Box 403)
        - Hard-edged (Box 403)
        - He Said, She Said, 2 folders (Box 403)
        - Heavy Petting (Box 403)
        - Hellmouth (Box 403)
        - His Like v. His Likes (Box 404)
        - Holy Land (Box 404)
        - Hospitality Industry, 2 folders (Box 404)
        - How to define "Alone" (Box 404)
        - In the Moment/Zen Moment (Box 404)
        - Incredible 'n' credible (Box 404)
        - Infamy (Box 404)
        - Impacting Status (Box 404)
        - Impeachment-ese (Box 404)
        - Issue (Box 404)
        - (dash) ite (Box 404)
        - Joe Six Pack (Box 404)
        - Kali (Box 404)
        - Kodak Moment (Box 404)
        - Leisure/recreation industry (Box 404)
        - Lodging Industry (Box 404)
        - Low the Temple Bar (Box 404)
        - Lowering the Bar (Box 405)
        - Maalox Moment (Box 405)
        - Masterly-Inactivity and Strategic Patience (Box 405)
        - Professor James McCawley (Box 405)
        - Millennium 5 (Box 405)
        - Millennium 6 (Box 405)
        - Mistakes 1998 (Box 405)
        - Mistakes 1999 (Box 405)
        - Misprision (Box 405)
        - Money terms, 2 folders (Box 405)
        - Moment- general (Box 405)
        - Mother wit (Box 405)
        - Motherhood and the Apple Pie (Box 405)
        - Move On (Box 405)
        - Mumbo Jumbo (Box 405)
        - Name that Nation (Box 406)
        - Nanny and Au Pair (Box 406)
        - Near Elderly, 2 folders (Box 406)
        - New York-ese (Box 406)
        - New York stylebook, 2 folders (Box 406)
        - Noir (Box 406)
        - Nutraceuticals v. Nutriceuticals (Box 406)
        - Obloquy (Box 406)
        - Obnubilate (Box 406)
        - Occam's Razor (Box 406)
        - Of High Moment (Box 406)
        - "On the Lam" (Box 406)
        - Ole English Used in the South (Box 406)
        - Opt out (Box 406)
        - Oxymorons (Box 406)
        - Paparazzi (Box 407)
        - "Pardon" terms (Box 407)
        - Parse (Box 407)
        - Patients' Bill of Rights (Box 407)
        - Permission edits, 2 folders (Box 407)
        - Picture Gallery, "Swimsuits through the Ages" (Box 407)
        - Poetic Allusion Watch (PAW) (Box 407)
        - Proffer (Box 407)
        - Purposeful/purposefully (Box 407)
        - Pushing it (Box 407)
        - Ratchet (noun) or (adjective) (Box 407)
        - Ratchet effect (Box 407)
        - Ratchet up (Box 407)
        - Report back (Box 407)
        - The Republic of Vermont (Box 407)
        - Retronyms (Box 407)
        - Revealed/disclosed (Box 407)
        - Rip-tootin (Box 407)
        - Rule of Thumb, 2 folders (Box 407)
        - Rush to Judgement (Box 407)
        - Safire v. Siegal (Box 407)
        - Scalia, Grammarian and Lexicographer (Box 408)
        - Snippers and PAW (Box 408)
        - Schwonk (Box 408)
        - Scot-free (Box 408)
        - SCOTUS (Box 408)
        - Scribble/scribbling (Box 408)
        - Senior moment (Box 408)
        - Safire on sexist language (Box 408)
        - Adjectives for males (Box 408)
        - Shameless, shameful (Box 408)
        - Shvakh (Box 408)
        - Short shrift (Box 408)
        - Sino (Box 408)
        - Skank (Box 408)
        - Slobo the Thug (Box 408)
        - Slow Walk (Box 408)
        - Smell a rat (Box 408)
        - Sobriquet (Box 408)
        - Social climber (Box 408)
        - Sooner, Rather than Later (Box 408)
        - Sorry and Topsy (Box 408)
        - Special (Box 408)
        - Sports teams (Box 408)
        - Sports teams and Plural or Singular verbs (Box 408)
        - Stake in the Ground (Box 408)
        - Star Chamber (Box 409)
        - Stock Market Plunge (Box 409)
        - Stump-Compounding (Box 409)
        - Suborn (Box 409)
        - Suck'em ins (Box 409)
        - Summer words (Box 409)
        - SWAG (Box 409)
        - Swimsuits edition (Box 409)
        - Swole (Box 409)
        - Syllogoid (Box 409)
        - Teen slang, 3 folders (Box 409)
        - That v. who (Box 409)
        - Third way (Box 409)
        - Thong (Box 409)
        - Thug Life (Box 410)
        - Tinker's Dam (Box 410)
        - Top 10 in the radio (Box 410)
        - Topsy (Box 410)
        - Touch base (Box 410)
        - Totally (Box 410)
        - Transparency (Box 410)
        - Trunk Show, 2 folders (Box 410)
        - Tut-tutting (Box 410)
        - Twilight Zone/zoned out (Box 410)
        - Untoward (Box 410)
        - USA, 2 folders (Box 410)
        - Victim's Bill of Rights (Box 410)
        - Voter's Bill of Rights (Box 410)
        - Ward Heeler (Box 410)
        - Ware off (Box 410)
        - We/us (Box 410)
        - Weapons of Mass Destruction, 2 folders (Box 410)
        - Webmaster (Box 410)
        - White-shoe Noodle (Box 410)
        - Whole Cloth (Box 411)
        - The Whole Shebang (Box 411)
        - Wild Asses (Box 411)
        - Wiser than us v. Wiser than we (Box 411)
        - X-mas Gifts of Gab (Box 411)
        - X-mas plugs (Box 411)
        - Y2K, 2 folders (Box 411)
      - Sampling (Box 411)
      - Terry Allen art files (Box 411)
      - Title suggestions (Box 411)
      - Thank-you letters (Box 411)
      - Setting copy, 5 folders (Box 411)
      - Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 412)
      - Working copy, 7 folders (Box 412)
    - On Language
      - Review and working copy, 2 folders (Box 413)
    - Safire's New Political Dictionary, 4th edition
      - Research notes
        - Abominable no-man (Box 413)
        - Advance man (Box 413)
        - Advice and consent (Box 413)
        - Amen corner (Box 413)
        - Amiable dunce (Box 413)
        - Animal spirits (Box 413)
        - Ankle-biters (Box 413)
        - Arena (Box 413)
        - Ask not (Box 413)
        - AuH2O=1964 (Box 413)
        - Balloon goes up (Box 413)
        - (dash) bashing (Box 413)
        - Beltway bandits (Box 413)
        - Big foot (Box 413)
        - Black power (Box 413)
        - Bloviate (Box 413)
        - Boll weevil (Box 413)
        - Boom (Box 413)
        - Bracketing (Box 413)
        - Bravo Zulu (Box 413)
        - Briefing book (Box 413)
        - Bubba factor (Box 413)
        - Bubba vote (Box 413)
        - Bullet vote (Box 413)
        - Cautiously optimistic (Box 413)
        - Character assassin (Box 413)
        - Character issue (Box 413)
        - Charisma (Box 413)
        - City on a hill (Box 413)
        - Closed shop (Box 413)
        - Clothespin vote (Box 413)
        - Cloud-Cuckoo-Land (Box 413)
        - Cold war (Box 413)
        - Confederate (Box 413)
        - Conservative (Box 413)
        - Contrarian (Box 413)
        - Convention bounce (Box 413)
        - Conventional wisdom (Box 413)
        - Crackdown (Box 413)
        - Creative federalism (Box 413)
        - Crunch (Box 413)
        - Daisy spot (Box 413)
        - Dead-cat bounce (Box 413)
        - Decouple (Box 413)
        - Defining moment (Box 413)
        - Detente (Box 413)
        - Devil is in the details (Box 413)
        - Dope story (Box 413)
        - Double dipping (Box 413)
        - Doves (Box 413)
        - Draw a line in the sand (Box 413)
        - Dustbin of history (Box 413)
        - Eastern Establishment (Box 413)
        - Egghead (Box 413)
        - Eleventh commandment (Box 413)
        - Empowerment (Box 413)
        - Ethnic cleansing (Box 413)
        - Ethnic purity (Box 413)
        - Ethnics (Box 413)
        - Extremism (Box 413)
        - Face time (Box 413)
        - Fallback position (Box 413)
        - Fatally flawed (Box 413)
        - Feeding frenzy (Box 413)
        - Fellow traveler (Box 413)
        - Finding (Box 413)
        - Finger on the button (Box 413)
        - Finlandization (Box 413)
        - Fire in the belly (Box 413)
        - First lady (Box 413)
        - Forty acres and a mule (Box 413)
        - Free lunch (Box 413)
        - Get with the program (Box 413)
        - Glasnost (Box 413)
        - Glass ceiling (Box 413)
        - Gravitas (Box 413)
        - Great Society (Box 413)
        - Handlers (Box 413)
        - Happy camper (Box 413)
        - Hard line (Box 413)
        - Heft (Box 413)
        - Hegemony (Box 413)
        - Holistic (Box 413)
        - Hot button (Box 413)
        - Household word (Box 413)
        - Human rights (Box 413)
        - Hymie's ferry boat (Box 413)
        - Hyphenated America (Box 413)
        - I see construction (Box 413)
        - If by whiskey (Box 413)
        - If it ain't broke, don't fix it (Box 413)
        - If you can't stand the heat (Box 413)
        - Indispensable man (Box 413)
        - Ins and outs (Box 413)
        - Inside baseball (Box 413)
        - Invective, political (Box 413)
        - Kinder and gentler nation (Box 413)
        - Lame duck (Box 413)
        - Laws, facetious (Box 414)
        - Leak (Box 414)
        - Let asians fight asians (Box 414)
        - Let 'em eat cake (Box 414)
        - Level playing field (Box 414)
        - Like ugly on an ape (Box 414)
        - Little tin box (Box 414)
        - Make the world safe for democracy (Box 414)
        - Man on the wedding cake (Box 414)
        - Military-industrial complex (Box 414)
        - Miscalculate (Box 414)
        - Moving the goalposts (Box 414)
        - Mr. Nice Guy (Box 414)
        - Natural rights (Box 414)
        - New Frontier (Box 414)
        - New world order (Box 414)
        - (dash) nomics (Box 414)
        - Nonstarter (Box 414)
        - (dash) ocracy (Box 414)
        - October surprise (Box 414)
        - Old wine in new bottles (Box 414)
        - Operation (Box 414)
        - Opportunist (Box 414)
        - Out of loop (Box 414)
        - Participatory democracy (Box 414)
        - Peace at any price (Box 414)
        - Peace process (Box 414)
        - People of color (Box 414)
        - Piss ant (Box 414)
        - Pit-bull politics (Box 414)
        - Pocatello, you can't go back (Box 414)
        - Pocketbook issue (Box 414)
        - Policeman of the world (Box 414)
        - Politically correct (Box 414)
        - Power curve (Box 414)
        - Pro-choice (Box 414)
        - Proverbs and axioms, political (Box 414)
        - Pump-priming (Box 414)
        - Pushing the envelope (Box 414)
        - Putsch (Box 414)
        - Quick fix (Box 414)
        - Rabbi (Box 414)
        - Read my lips (Box 414)
        - Readout (Box 414)
        - Reclama (Box 414)
        - Red meat (Box 414)
        - Redheaded Eskimo Bill (Box 414)
        - Revanchism (Box 414)
        - Right to know (Box 414)
        - Rising tide lifts all the boats (Box 414)
        - Root and branch (Box 414)
        - Root, hog, or die (Box 414)
        - Rosie Scenario (Box 414)
        - Run between the raindrops (Box 414)
        - Safety net (Box 414)
        - Salutations (Box 414)
        - San Francisco Democrat (Box 414)
        - Scorched earth (Box 414)
        - Secret plan (Box 414)
        - Send them a message (Box 414)
        - Sharp elbows (Box 414)
        - Sheep in sheep's clothing (Box 414)
        - Ship of state (Box 414)
        - Short list (Box 414)
        - Single-issue politics (Box 414)